<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<sanity>
  <test TEST="Wi-Fi">
    Connect to a Wi-Fi network
  </test>
  <test TEST="Power On/Off">
    Check if the operator's power on/off animation (if required in GPRI) is installed
  </test>	
  <test TEST="Wallpaper">
    Check if all the operator wallpapers (if required in GPRI) are installed
  </test>
  <test TEST="UAP/UAS (User Agent Profile/String)">
    On LG Browser, open xhaus.com/headers and compare the UAP/UAS to model's UAP on LG's database
  </test>
  <test TEST="Android Icon">
    Check if each app has its own icon, not Android default
  </test>
  <test TEST="Operator APKs">
    Check if all operator APKs (if required in GPRI) are installed, in order and working
  </test>
  <test TEST="Embedded games">
    Check if all embedded games are installed and working properly as required in http://collab.lge.com/main/display/SCAI/05.+MT+-+Models. For D models, check http://10.193.225.22:8090/Views/View/Default.aspx
  </test>
  <test TEST="LG Smart World">
    1. 'LG Smart World' app is available for Argentina, Brazil and Mexico (except for Claro and Telcel operators). All other countries should not have this app.
    2. Factory reset the device and repeat the first procedure.
  </test>
  <test TEST="Network Mode">
    1. Check Network Mode String on GPRI and Network Mode Menu, then check if both are the same.
    2. The options 2G/3G/4G or LTE and 2G/3G must be "auto" or "automatico" at the end.		
  </test>
  <test TEST="Preset browser bookmarks">
    Check if all the operator bookmarks are installed in LG Browser (if required in GPRI)
  </test>
  <test TEST="Preset browser home page">
    If required in GPRI, check if LG Browser's home page is the same one as required by operator
  </test>
  <test TEST="SMS parameters">
    Check if the SMS parameters are the same as required by operator
  </test>
  <test TEST="Cell broadcasting">
    Check if cell broadcasting and its channels are according to GPRI
  </test>
  <test TEST="E-mail customisation">
    Check if all e-mail preset accounts are configured (if required in GPRI)
  </test>
  <test TEST="QFuse">
	Check if QFuse is enabled.
	* Pass -> QFuse is enabled
	* N/A -> QFuse is not accepted in the model under test
	* Fail -> QFuse is accepted in the model, but is disabled
	</test>
  <test TEST="E-mail (send)">
    Send an e-mail
  </test>
  <test TEST="E-mail (receive)">
    Receive an e-mail
  </test>
  <test TEST="Bluetooth">
    Connect to another device via Bluetooth
  </test>
  <test TEST="Camera (picture)">
    Take a picture
  </test>
  <test TEST="Camera (video)">
    Record a video
  </test>
  <test TEST="Gallery">
    Check if the picture and the video taken are stored in Gallery
  </test>
  <test TEST="MP3">
    Play, pause, rewind and fast-forward an MP3 file
  </test>
  <test TEST="Radio">
    Test the FM radio
  </test>
  <test TEST="Home screen">
    Check if all apps on home screen are working
  </test>
  <test TEST="Notification bar">
    Slide down the notification bar and test all functions 
  </test>
  <test TEST="Applications menu">
    Test all apps
  </test>
  <test TEST="FOTA menu">
    Check if the 2nd option under "Software upgrade" is checked
  </test>
  <test TEST="Flashlight widget">
    Check if the flashlight widget is working properly. (Note: if the device under test does not have this widget, download the Flashlight app on play store and test the widget
  </test>
  <test TEST="Google TTS">
    Check Google Text-to-Speech (voice search) is working
  </test>
  <test TEST="Google folder">
    [GMS below 3.0] The order of the apps in Google folder (home screen) must be as following: Chrome, Gmail, Google+, Maps, Play Music, Play Movies, Play Books, Play Newsstand, Play Games, Drive, YouTube, Photos, Hangouts
	[GMS 3.0] The order of the apps must be Google Search, Chrome, Gmail, Maps, YouTube, Drive, Play Music, Play Movies, Hangouts, Photos
	* To check whether it is GMS 3.0 or not, adb shell getprop ro.com.lge.mada
  </test>
  <test TEST="3G">
    Visit a website while connected to a 3G network
  </test>
  <test TEST="4G">
    1. With a real SIM card, activate flex test with the project's MCC/MNC
	2. Go to Settings > Mobile networks > Network model
	3. Check if the device's network mode matches the project's LTE mode as described in GPRI
	4. Visit a website while connected to a 4G network
  </test>
  <test TEST="Data network icon">
    Check if the data network icon in the notifications bar disappears when you turn off the data connection or connect to a Wi-Fi network
  </test>
  <test TEST="SMS (send)">
    Send an SMS
  </test>
  <test TEST="SMS (receive)">
    Receive an SMS
  </test>
  <test TEST="Call outgoing">
    Make a phone call
  </test>
  <test TEST="Call incoming">
    Receive a phone call
  </test>
</sanity>